♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Hey, welcome to Bonnie's
29th birthday party.
I ca... I can't keep this up.
She's 46.
Here, we brought you guys
an orchid from Trader Joe's,
because we don't know
or care about
any of your interests.
Well, I put together
some videos
for Bonnie's party.
Here we are on our honeymoon.
Yeah, Cabo was great.
We even went back
for our 10th anniversary.
Better wrap it up,
honey, tide's coming in.
Well, let's break for presents,
but after that, I'll show you
Susie's birth video,
and I'll tell you,
she fell out of there
like an orange out
of an old dress sock.
Ugh, I have to text Rupert
what a train wreck this is.
Hey, I want real things.
Kind of weird they're keeping
all our jackets in the tub.
Bonnie?
I told you, Joe,
when we're alone,
you can call me "Bonald."
No, i-it's me, Brian.
Is that your real name?
I mean, are you...
are you okay?
Sorry, am I
allowed on the bed?
I guess so.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I have something
in my eye.
Yes, you do.
It looks
like sadness.
Come on, you
can tell me.
I'm your
neighbor's dog.
I don't know.
It's just that
when I was young,
I had so many things
I wanted to do
with my life,
but now, I'm 46,
and all I've ever done
is take care of Joe.
And now you feel like
you never had a chance
to be your true self.
Yeah.
I know just how you feel.
I mean, I'm happy
that Peter found me
and gave me a home, but
sometimes I wonder
if I'd be happier
on my own.
Exactly.
It's like sometimes,
I feel...
Trapped?
No, I was going to say,
"like the Von Trapps."
You know, unable to leave
their home in Austria.
Oh. Well, that still
is remarkably close.
Thanks for being
so nice to me, Brian.
Why are you scratching
behind my ear?
I... I don't...
I don't know.
I thought it might
make you feel better.
It does feel kind of nice.
You're a good girl.
You're going to be okay.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I did... I didn't...
I didn't mean...
No, it's okay.
Um... I better go downstairs
before Joe realizes
I'm gone.
And before Peter
gets into the stuff
that's not for the party.
Aw, Halloween candy!
Peter, get out
of the pantry.
Ah, I can't believe I just
kissed my friend's wife.
I'm a bigger scumbag than Spock.
I heard that there
was a Romulan ship
spotted in our sector,
which means...
Hey, hey.
Kids, this morning,
Principal Shepherd
wanted to say a few words.
Thank you, Mrs. Abbott.
Uh, before I start,
are these the normal kids
or kind of the
"dur, dur" ones?
It's a healthy mix.
Good morning, children.
It's that time
of the year again
to fulfill your
community service requirement
by signing up
for volunteer work.
Do we get to choose
our own jobs?
No, no, no, no.
The jobs will be
assigned randomly
but the cooler
and prettier students
have the better jobs.
For instance, blonde
chick in the third row
will wash my car
this afternoon
while, Little Miss Frumpkin
with all the questions,
will work in an
old folks' home.
Is "frumpkin" good?
No, no.
Brian, what are you
doing up so late?
Ah, I'm having
trouble sleeping.
I got to tell you something.
I kissed Bonnie last night.
What?!
I know! I know!
It was a huge mistake.
So let's just do two
or three high-fives
and then forget
it ever happened.
Brian, if Joe finds out,
he'll kill you.
Yeah, no kidding.
That's why you can't
tell anybody.
Promise me.
Oh, don't worry.
Don't worry.
I'm great at
keeping secrets.
Well, except for
that one time
you discovered
my hidden shame.
Peter?
Brian.
I'm, uh, I'm sorry.
I'm one of these guys now.
I'm sorry, Brian, I'm sorry.
Mrs. Parkhurst?
I'm Meg, your new
student volunteer.
Oh, you must be my
new student volunteer.
Yeah, I just said that.
What's your name, dear?
It's Meg.
Can... can I get
a new person?
Nonsense, come in,
and between you and me,
I hate my new
student volunteer.
That ugly little Meg.
She says she's a girl,
but she certainly has
a boy's body odor.
Oh, come on in.
Peter, Joe and Bonnie
are here for game night.
Game night?
Yeah, I figured it was
the least we could do,
since you pulled up
a beheading video on your phone
at their party
and showed it to everyone.
It was really more about
how loud my phone can get.
Peter, we're doing this.
All right.
But the Operation game
is out of batteries,
so I'll have to
make the noise.
You hear that?
That's the sound
of bad surgery.
All right,
I'm awesome at charades.
Guys are going first.
Okay, go.
Uh, About a Boy.
Uh, Four...
Four Weddings and a Funeral.
Uh, Nine Months.
Notting Hill.
Yes, it was Notting Hill.
I'm going to go
get more wine.
Oh, hey.
Hi, Brian.
Um, listen,
about the other night.
You haven't told anyone,
have you?
No, no, of course not.
I was going to
ask if you had.
Hey, Brian,
can you bring me up a snack?
I'm supposed to be in bed.
Look, the other
night was great,
but it was a mistake.
You're right.
Oh, man, what?
Yeah, I me... I mean, there's...
there's definitely some kind
of connection between us, but...
I felt it, too,
but maybe in another life, huh?
Yeah, I guess
you're right.
This could never work.
Like porn movies
before sound.
Ooh.
Oh, there you are.
Come on, Bonnie,
it's Joe's turn.
Okay, here we go,
uh, uh, crippled guy...
uh, cheating wife...
uh, uh, cheating wife
of a crippled guy...
Uh, dog... some... something
with a dog... uh, dog kiss.
I-I-I, uh, I think
that's, uh, time.
Your, your turn is over.
Oh, sounds like, uh, sounds like
dog kisses crippled guy's wife
at your party.
Wait, wait! I know it.
The other night at your party,
Brian kissed Bonnie.
What?
Bonnie, is this true?
Oh, my God.
I know, making out with a dog?
Can you even imagine a woman who
possibly does that for real?
Uh, hi, Joe.
Hi, Brian.
Look, I-I want to apologize
for what happened.
I-I-I didn't mean
to kiss Bonnie.
Everybody had a little
too much to drink.
It-it just happened.
Uh, I hope we're still cool.
Hey, don't worry about it.
It was a crazy party.
We ran out of salsa.
How do you run out of salsa?
Anyway, we're good.
Really?
Oh, thank God.
I-I-I was worried you'd be mad.
Mad? At my buddy, Brian?
Not a chance.
Hey, is that your car?
What? No!
Wh-what's he doing?
My car was parked legally.
Huh. Well, maybe your car
violated some sort
of unspoken boundary.
One that nobody
bothers to codify
because it's just
common decency.
Hey, Joe, is that the guy?
Read your text, Jerry.
Not supposed to say
you know me.
Well, I hope your day
gets better, Brian,
but, uh, I wouldn't
count on it.
Boy, it wasn't easy
Mrs. Parkhurst,
but I think we
got the nail
that was poking
through your slipper.
Well, you strike
me as someone
who's never going
to get married,
that's for sure.
Now get me my itch cream.
Is it in the drawer?
Shut up!
I'm trying to
hum atonally.
Ugh.
Here's your cream.
See you Thursday.
Oh, my God,
I can't believe I stole this.
You know what?
I don't feel bad.
That woman's a nightmare.
Ooh, I should text this
to my best friend.
Sick brooch!
Adam, are you done with
that mayor homework, yet?
It's called a bill, Mom.
Hey, Brian,
I, uh, feel that things
have been awkward between us,
but just to show you
there's no hard feelings,
can I buy you a drink?
You know what?
Sure, thanks.
What the hell happened?
Ah! How do I walk?!
Are these forever?!
I also rubbed my butt on you
while you were unconscious.
I like to put stuff online.
Meg, Mom said that...
Hey, what's all this stuff?
Stuff I stole from
the old folks' home.
But you should see
how they treat me.
Meg, that's no excuse.
Stealing is just plain...
Oh, my God, is that
someone else's glasses?
I love wearing other
people's glasses.
Do I look like I stole
atomic secrets?
You do.
Wow, this is awesome.
I want in.
And there's the
splitting headache
from wearing someone
else's glasses.
Okay, Chris, here's a room
I haven't hit, yet.
Here, follow my lead.
Who's there?
Why are you in my room?
Oh, hi.
You died, and I'm here
to take you to heaven.
Um, upsy-daisy, here we go.
Well, now that
I'm in heaven...
Hurry, take everything,
and be quick or we'll
be in bigger trouble
than a fat guy
at a water park.
Come on, Dad, let's go
on the water slide.
I can't fit.
I'm afraid
I'll get stuck.
I'll just go in
the lazy river.
But, Dad...
No, son, this is
the life I've chosen.
♪ When your day is long ♪
♪ And the night ♪
♪ The night is yours alone ♪
♪ When you're sure you... ♪
♪ Of this life... ♪
Guys, thanks again
for doing this.
Joe has been making
my life hell.
Of course.
All right,
now when Joe gets here
we're just going to tell him
he needs to lighten up on Brian,
and then we'll all talk
this thing out
so we can move past it.
And then I get
to show my card trick?
If there's time.
Let's make this quick.
What's going on?
What's all this?
Joe, we all know what happened
and we're here for you.
But we think that you're taking
this revenge on Brian
just a little too far.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, come on.
It's...it's like
enough is enough.
The Triscuits are
the rosemary kind,
not the regular kind.
Me? I'm not the guy
who violated the sanctity
of someone else's marriage.
Well, you make a
good point, Joe,
and you're right,
this is Brian.
We all know
he don't care
where he gets
his wick wet.
Just ask
Quagmire's father.
Okay, we might be getting
a little off track, here.
Yeah, yeah, Brian's right.
Joe, you're out of control.
Even though Brian's
been trying
to do my wife for years,
and on some level,
I hate him for it.
Oh, Brian's a complete dick,
we all know that,
but I think we're
losing sight of the point
that Bonnie's a weird slut
who's always letting you know
she's open for business.
What? When am I doing that?
Oh, come on, when are
you not doing that?
With that
boo-boo-baby voice,
and that
still-breastfeeding rack.
Give me some of that!
I'm Bonnie's friend,
but she could
sometimes get the mail
in something other than a robe.
Okay, so we're all
in agreement,
Bonnie and Brian
are terrible people.
Quagmire, I want you
to think of a card,
but do not tell me what it is.
Okay, enough.
How dare any of you
criticize Bonnie?
For years, she gave
up her own dreams
to take care of Joe.
And yeah, maybe
she kissed me.
Maybe she needed to
because she feels
so trapped in
her marriage.
It's true.
No one ever takes the time
to ask how I feel.
Brian's the only one.
They don't get us, Bonnie,
and you deserve
better than this.
We both do.
You know what?
Let's get out of here.
Wow, we are zero for two
on interventions today.
I'm not changing for nobody.
You're no... you're the ones
with the problems.
Ah, we did it.
We don't need those
narrow-minded losers.
This is so exciting.
We can finally live the
lives we've always wanted.
Like, I can finally start
my jewelry design business
making earrings for tweens.
Listen, hear that?
That is the sound
of not making
an enormous mistake.
I think I hear it.
Oh, hang on, looks
like we need gas.
So do you have,
like, a credit card?
Nope and no cash, either,
but I don't care.
I couldn't stand
another moment with Joe.
It was torture just watching
him do a crossword puzzle.
Hey, Bonnie, what's a
five-letter word for marriage?
Fraud.
Uh, it's got to start
with a "U".
Union.
Boy, you stink at this.
Boy, it's just so
comforting to be here
surrounded by
other people's memories.
Back into the
sleeve with you.
Can you hand me
another nylon
that I use as a sock
with my huge beige shoe?
Sure, and can you
hand me that ashtray?
I might fire up
this pipe again.
Chris, that's not
an ashtray.
That's an urn
for someone's ashes.
Really?
Yeah, you've been
putting your pipe out
in some guy.
Oh, my God,
what are we doing?
I feel awful.
We need to give
everything back.
Oh, you're right.
We need to do
the right thing.
Like the dad
from Small Wonder.
All right, Vickie,
time to shut you down
for the night.
Good-night.
See you tomorrow.
Nah.
She's really gone,
and she took little
Susie with her.
I miss that baby
more than anything.
Oh, I guess she
left it here.
Joe, I want you to know,
I will not support
that relationship.
If Brian and Bonnie
get married,
I will not go.
Although, Brian might want
me to be his best man.
Then I'd have to go,
and I'd have to dance.
It would be weird to
be best man and not dance.
And I'd have
to give a toast,
and say that Bonnie's
the best thing
that ever happened to him.
You know, she is
the best thing
that ever happened to him,
but don't worry, Joe.
I'll only refer to you
as Bonnie's ex.
You know, like,
"Bonnie has an ex,
but Brian marks the spot."
Oh, Peter, that's good.
Thanks, babe.
I hope Brian and Bonnie
are as happy as us.
To Brian and Bonnie.
Bad news:
the teenage runaways
at table four were
not big tippers.
We just need enough
money to get to Taos.
That's like the capital
of making and selling
your own jewelry.
Okay, enough about
the jewelry.
Do you even know
how to make it?
I know how to
make jewelry.
I just don't know
how to make the
metal go into shapes.
Hey, you know what'd be great?
If you could talk with even
a little bit of inflection
to your voice,
so it doesn't sound so much
like a power sander.
Screw you.
You tweet things that
aren't worth tweeting.
Well, I'm sorry,
but Kim Kardashian
did get famous
for making a sex tape.
We all know that.
That's not yours.
And stop breathing
through your mouth.
It's really annoying.
I'm panting.
That's how I sweat,
you dumb bitch.
No, it isn't.
Dogs sweat
through their paws.
You're such a
know-it-all, Brian,
you don't even know
about your own body.
At least I've
had an orgasm.
Wow, I am sorry.
Look, th-this isn't us.
This is just the no food
and sleeping in
a car talking.
We can make this work,
like couples who
meet on Craigslist.
You're not what you look like
in your picture.
Let's get this over with.
I wonder which one of us
is the murderer?
Okay, we ditch this stuff
in the day room,
and then I'm done
with my volunteer hours
and we never come
back here again.
Mrs. Parkhurst?
Look at you two,
stealing from the elderly.
You're worse than that
Juliette Lewis
who makes out with dogs.
Wait, is that a real thing?
Where did you hear that?
What are your sources?
Listen, we're very sorry
we stole from you,
but you have it all back now,
so we cool, right?
You know I should call
the police on you.
The police?!
Or maybe, instead,
we do things my way.
What's that?
You will spend time with us
every afternoon after school,
doing jigsaw puzzles,
reading us the newspaper,
listening to poorly remembered
stories that have no point.
You monster.
Sit down.
Now I feel some
dementia coming.
Feed me pudding
while I grip
your wrist in terror.
Ah, this isn't
my house.
See, if I make
under 20 grand
for 20 years,
my film school debt
just goes away.
That's a government rule.
Bonnie?
Joe?
How did you find me?
Love is a powerful compass.
Any time I quiet my mind
and clear my heart,
it always leads me to you.
Plus, dirtbag here has
a chip in his ear.
I do?
Damn it.
No wonder Peter's so good
at hide-and-seek.
You're under the canoe
in Quagmire's yard.
Son of a bitch!
Bonnie, I understand
now why you left.
Over the years, I probably have
become too dependent on you,
and I'm sorry if you've
had to put your dreams
on hold because of me.
Oh, Joe.
But I'm here to
fight for you, Bonnie.
And if you're willing
to come back home,
I promise I'll spend the rest
of my days taking care of you,
just the way you've
always taken care of me.
Of course,
I want to come home, Joe.
I love you.
Wow, I guess just
call me Cupid, huh?
You're welcome.
Ow! Damn it!
Hey, Bri, came to try
that apple pie
you were texting about.
Oh, you're shot.
Well, Chris and I sure
learned a lot this week.
Ha, you think you
learned a lot.
I had quite
an adventure.
You know what guys?
We only got like
15 seconds left.
We're going to have
to do these at the same time.
Let's race.
And... go.
So Chris and I learned
that just 'cause people are old,
that doesn't mean
you should steal from them.
Bonnie didn't let you
stir the paint, did she?
No. But I am done messing
around with neighbors' wives.
Here's an invitation
to Donna's birthday party.
'Cause maybe then I'd like it.
Hey, let me see that.
You rascal.
Same old Meg.
And the winner is:
Nobody.
Especially not you.
Good night.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru